hi today we will be talking about term
insurance
presenting to you a term insurance plan
from Aditya birla Sun Life called as
Life Shield plan so let's understand
Life Shield plan with an example Rahul
whose age is around 48 years
Smitha whose age is around 45 years now
they have opted for a limited premium
paying term of around 10 years
the coverage will be there till the age
of around 85 years now round switch is
around 48 years will be covered for next
37 years that is till the age of around
85 years
now Rahul will be paying the premium
money for 10 years from 48 years to 57
years and the premium
for them will be around 1 lakh 15 168
rupees Rahul will be having a coverage
of around 50 lakhs Smitha will be having
a foreign
the total premium paid by them per year
will be 1 lakh fifteen thousand one
sixty eight rupees now let's assume that
okay Rahul has paid a previous premium
second year has been diminished with a
terminal illness due to which the
company will be paying 50 of the same
Institute of the rahula that is 25x is
given to the
family members 2 for the treatment of
rahula so after six months when Rahul is
no more
remaining 50 of this commercial that is
25 axis once again given to the family
members
Still Still
the policy continues for Smitha she did
not have to pay the further premiums
which should have been paid by rahola
Smitha will be having a coverage till
the age of around 85 years now in in
case if Smitha dies at the age of around
84th year also her family members will
be getting around 25 lakhs so
term insurance will be suggested to the
customers to protect the future of the
future dreams of their family and to
protect the income to know more about
term insurance or any other insurance
plan you can call us on double
n800-1270 thanks
foreign